{
  "levels": {
    "level1": [
      {
        "question": "2 + 2 = ?",
        "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "3 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": ["7", "8", "9", "10"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "5 - 2 = ?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "9 - 7 = ?",
        "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "6 / 2 = ?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "7 * 1 = ?",
        "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "10 + 10 = ?",
        "answers": ["15", "20", "25", "30"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "8 - 5 = ?",
        "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "6 * 3 = ?",
        "answers": ["12", "18", "24", "30"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      { "question": "4 + 4 = ?", "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"], "correct": 2 }
    ],
    "level2": [
      {
        "question": "12 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": ["18", "19", "20", "21"],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "14 - 4 = ?",
        "answers": ["9", "10", "11", "12"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "5 * 3 = ?",
        "answers": ["15", "16", "17", "18"],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "9 / 3 = ?",
        "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "11 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": ["21", "22", "23", "24"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "15 - 5 = ?",
        "answers": ["9", "10", "11", "12"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "7 * 2 = ?",
        "answers": ["12", "13", "14", "15"],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "18 - 9 = ?",
        "answers": ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "20 / 5 = ?",
        "answers": ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "6 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
        "correct": 1
      }
    ]
  }
}
